{
    "question": "Fill in the gaps from thes words : energetic,shy funny,and selfish\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>isi celah dari kata-kata ini : energik , malu lucu , dan egois</p>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. funny</p><p>2. shy</p><p>3. energetic</p><p>4. selfish</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>1. Fill in the gaps. Use the words in the box !</p><p>a. My uncle loves to tell jokes to make us laugh. He is . . . . . . . .</p><p>b. She never talks to a stranger. She is very . . . . . . . . . . .</p><p>c. I like doing sports and physical activities. I\u2019m very . . . . . . . . . . . . . .</p><p>d. Don\u2019t just think of yourself, that\u2019s so . . . . . . . .</p><p></p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "2-the-girls-are-watching-movie-in-the-cinema-547",
            "question": "2. (+)The girls are watching movie in the\r\ncinema.\r\n(-)..\r\n(?)...\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>(-) The girls aren&#039;t watching movie in the cinema</p><p>(?) Are The girls watching movie in the\n</p><p>cinema?</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "27-desi-do-you-mind-if-i-use-your-pen-to-sign-this-paper-jus-353",
            "question": "27. Desi    \"Do you mind if I use your pen to sign\r\nthis paper?\"\r\n\"Just a moment. I haven't finished\r\nwriting my curriculum vitae.\"\r\nArif\r\nWhat does the woman want?\r\nA To borrow a pen.\r\nB. To buy some paper,\r\nC. To write an article.\r\nD. To ask his paper,\r\nE. To finish her writing\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Artinya</p><p>Apakah kamu tidak keberatan kalau aku pinjam pulpen kamu buat tandatangani kertas ini?</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>A.To borrow a pen </p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>Desi ingin meminjam pena milik arif tapi,</p><p>Arif sedang menggunakan penanya untuk menyelesaikan tugasnya.</p><p></p><p>See you at the next answer </p><p>Pawuuu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "this-text-is-for-questions-5-6-sasha-sorry-i-cant-come-to-your-734",
            "question": "This text is for questions 5-6    Sasha, sorry I can't come to your house to\r\nnight to do the Science project as we have\r\nplanned. My grandmother just came and she\r\nwants me to accompany her to my aunt's\r\nhouse. I will meet you at school tomorrow.\r\nErinda\r\n__________________________\r\n6. \"... she wants me to accompany her...\r\nThe underlined word refers to...\r\nA. Sasha's grandmother\r\nB. Erinda's grandmother\r\nC. My grandmother\r\nD. My aunt\r\nhis text is for questions 7-8\r\nANNOUNCEMENT\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B. Erinda&#039;s grandmother</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-write-a-procedure-text-akl-how-to-make-a-label-774",
            "question": "1. write a procedure text :\r\nAKL ( how to make a label)\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. tulis teks prosedur :</p><p>AKL (cara membuat label) </p><p></p><p><strong>ini</strong><strong> </strong><strong>terjem</strong><strong>ahan</strong><strong> </strong><strong>nya</strong><strong> </strong><strong>,</strong><strong> </strong><strong>aja</strong><strong> </strong></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "34-what-does-the-song-tell-us-about-a-the-writer-want-to-go-to-911",
            "question": "34. What does the song tell us about?    A. The writer want to go to Paris and Rome\r\nB. The writer want to go home\r\nC. Aero plane\r\nD. Summer day\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>c.aero plane</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalo salah,semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tuliskan-manfaat-air-yang-ditemukan-ditempat-tempat-berikut-a-t-575",
            "question": "Tuliskan manfaat air yang ditemukan ditempat tempat berikut!    A. Tanah\r\nB. Sumur\r\nC. Laut \r\nD. Sungai\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>c. laut</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu:)</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. Air Tanah berfungsi Memenuhi berbagai keperluan rumah tangga, seperti mandi, memasak, minum, dan mencuci. Irigasi pertanian, pada sawah petani yang letaknya jauh dari sumber air seperti pada sungai umumnya kemudian akan membuat sumur bor untuk mencukupi berbagai kebutuhan air tanaman pertanian.</p><p>B. fungsi air sumur </p><p>    1. Meminimalisir Genangan Air Hujan</p><p>    2. mengurangi risiko banjir</p><p>    3. menambah cadangan air tanah</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf cuma segini, selebihnya cari di google ya kak</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-is-the-climax-of-the-strory-true-friends-once-upon-a-time-909",
            "question": "What is the climax of the strory?    True Friends\r\n\r\n Once upon a time, there were two close friends who were walking through the forest together. They knew that anything dangerous can happen any time in the forest. So they promised each other that they would always be together in any case of danger.\r\n\r\n Suddenly, they saw a large bear getting closer toward them. One of them climbed a nearby tree at once. But unfortunately the other one did not know how to climb up the tree. So being led by his common sense, he lay down on the ground breathless and pretended to be a dead man.\r\n\r\n The bear came near the one who was lying on the ground. It smelt in his ears, and slowly left the place because the bears do not want to touch the dead creatures. After that, the friend on the tree came down and asked his friend that was on the ground, \"Friend, what did the bear whisper into your ears?\" The other friend replied, \"Just now the bear advised me not to believe a false friend.\"\r\n\r\n Moral of the Story- A true friend in need is a friend indeed",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Apa klimaks dari cerita tersebut?</p><p></p><p>Teman sejati</p><p></p><p>Alkisah, ada dua orang sahabat yang sedang berjalan bersama di hutan. Mereka tahu bahwa segala sesuatu yang berbahaya dapat terjadi kapan saja di hutan. Jadi mereka berjanji satu sama lain bahwa mereka akan selalu bersama dalam keadaan bahaya apa pun.</p><p></p><p>Tiba-tiba, mereka melihat seekor beruang besar mendekat ke arah mereka. Salah satu dari mereka memanjat pohon terdekat sekaligus. Namun sayangnya yang satunya tidak tahu bagaimana cara memanjat pohon tersebut. Jadi dibimbing oleh akal sehatnya, dia berbaring di tanah dengan terengah-engah dan berpura-pura menjadi orang mati.</p><p></p><p>Beruang itu mendekati orang yang terbaring di tanah. Itu tercium di telinganya, dan perlahan meninggalkan tempat itu karena beruang tidak mau menyentuh makhluk mati. Setelah itu, teman di pohon itu turun dan bertanya kepada temannya yang ada di tanah, \"Teman, apa yang dibisikkan beruang ke telingamu?\" Teman yang lain menjawab, \"Baru saja beruang itu menasihati saya untuk tidak mempercayai teman palsu.\"</p><p></p><p>Moral of the Story- Teman sejati yang membutuhkan adalah teman sejati.</p><p></p><p>Semoga membantu^^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "teacher-how-are-you-studentthank-you-828",
            "question": "Teacher :how are you?\r\n Student:.....,thank you",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>i&#039;m fine</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>alternatif lain:</p><p>I am doing fine</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>I am good, thank you</p><p></p><p>But the answer is depending on how your feeling. If you feel bad than say you aren&#039;t feel good but if you are good then say it that you are feeling good</p><p></p><p>Simple by hucas</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "quiz-aldo-left-his-favourite-restaurant-at-11-oclock-it-wa-334",
            "question": "Quiz ;)    Aldo left his favourite restaurant at 11 o\u2019clock. It was warm evening and decided to walk along the beach. Suddenly, four masked girls aged about seventeen came up to \u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026 and asked for the street.\r\n\r\nA. Him\r\nB. Her\r\nC. You\r\nD. Me\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>\u27a1\ufe0f A Him </p><p></p><h3>Question</h3><p>Aldo left his favourite restaurant at 11 o\u2019clock. It was warm evening and decided to walk along the beach. Suddenly, four masked girls aged about seventeen came up to \u2026\u2026and asked for the street.</p><p>A. Him</p><p>B. Her</p><p>C. You</p><p>D. Me</p><p></p><h3>Translat </h3><p>Aldo meninggalkan restoran favoritnya pada pukul 11.  Itu adalah malam yang hangat dan memutuskan untuk berjalan di sepanjang pantai.  Tiba-tiba, empat gadis bertopeng berusia sekitar tujuh belas datang ke \u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026\u2026 dan meminta jalan.</p><p></p><p> A. Dia</p><p> B. Dia</p><p> C. Anda</p><p> D. Saya</p><p></p><h3>Answer</h3><p>A. Him</p><p></p><h3>Explanation</h3><p>Explain as a pronoun he is male is him, he, .</p><p>while the pronoun in female her, she,</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "9-please-return-my-jacket-soon-okay-the-underlined-word-means-a-398",
            "question": "9. Please return my jacket soon. Okay    The underlined word means\r\nA Let something drop\r\nB Give something back\r\nC. Make something better\r\nD Send something home\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B. give something back</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>return berarti mengembalikan</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p> B give something back</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>it says return so it Means give something back bc</p><p>return =give back or something else whatever</p><p>smoga membantu :/</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}